You don't have a girlfriend now, right?
7A いっせい (ゆかり) -星さん今 フリーなんですよね?
I heard that your only love is ramen, and you don't have a girlfriend.
ラーメン一筋で 好きな人もいないって しない
Jeez, what should I do?
(一星)いやどうしよう
Hey! What're you doing?
なお (菜緒)いやちょっ...
This here is my girlfriend!
(一星) こいつ俺の彼女
So, I'm sorry, I can't go out with you.
だからごめん 君とは付き合えないんだ
Yow! That's hot!
(鍋を落とす音) (徹平)あちっ!
I put my hand right in the pot!
鍋直接触っちゃつた
It started about a month ago.
(一星)始まりは1ヶ月前
Just before closing she... Yukari...
閉店間際にあの人… ゆかりさんが
I don't know why, but she was crying while she ate her ramen.
何だか知らないけど 泣きながらラーメン食っててさ
I wanted to cheer her up somehow.
俺何とかして励ましたくて
So I gave her a free soft-boiled egg.
味玉サービスしたんだ
Here. It's on the house.
(一星) サービスだよお客さん
That's all?
それだけ?
The next day
その翌日
she said, "Please be my boyfriend."
“付き合ってください”って 言われてさ
I turned her down, but she won't give up.
いや断ったんだけど つにんに 全然諦めてくれなくて
But even so, why did you lie like that?
(菜緒)だとしても あ ,ウソつくなんて
That's not like you at all, Issei.
何かいっちゃんらしくないよ
But lately Yukari's been phoning our house,
(一星)でもゆかりさん うちに電話してきたり
and waiting for me outside.
待ち伏せまでするようになって
She was waiting out front when we came to prep.
(徹平)昨日は仕込みの時間に 表にいたしな
At prep time? That's 5 a.m.!
(菜緒)仕込みの時間って 5時?
If things get any worse,
(一星)俺これ以上 エスカレートすると
I won't be able to concentrate on work.
仕事に集中できねーよ
Then why don't you flat out reject her?
うえはら (上原)だったらもっと 京) たつた はっきり断ればいいだろう
It doesn't matter if she ends up hating you.
嫌われてもいいから 相手が納得するまで
Yukari...
(一星)ゆかりさん
she tells me that our ramen is really delicious.
うちのラーメンを おいしいって言ってくれたんだ
I can't be so cold to a customer that says good things about our ramen.
うちのラーメン 褒めてくれる客に
Issei!
一星
You are truly my son! You're the real Evening Star!
さすが俺のせがれだ 俺の一番星の一星だ!
Father!
(一星)親父!
Uhm...
あつあの…
-Oh, wait. -Huh?
(一星)ちょっと (徹平)ん? よ? ちん
-I beg you! -What?
(一星)頼む! (菜緒)え?
While you're here at the shop...
この店にいる間
No, just while Yukari is here,
いやゆかりさんが 来てる時だけでいい
please act like you're my girlfriend.
俺の彼女のフリしてくれ
Please!
頼む
Don't do that.
やめてよ
When you bow down to me like that,
何かいっちゃんに 頭下げられると
it feels so wrong.
調子狂うっていうか
Oh, yeah.
そうだ
You're right.
そうだよな
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
The money you owe for the broken dishes is $12,000.
お前が割った丼の 弁償代120万
Who's letting you secretly pay that off in installments?
内緒で分割にしてやってるのは 誰だっけ?
Wait a minute!
いや…
That has nothing to do with this!
それとこれとは別でしょうが
What are you whispering about?
(徹平)ん? 何コソコソ話してんだ?
Oh, nothing.
あついや…
At any rate, I've already got a proper boyfriend.
とにかく私には ちゃんとれっきとした彼氏が…
I can't deal with you guys.
(上原)付き合いきれね
Hey! Wait for me, Uehara!
(菜緒)ちょっちょっと ちょっと待ってよ上原君!
You're OK with that, Uehara?
ねえ上原君はいいの?
I can act the part of another guy's girlfriend?
私が他の人の か…彼女でも
I don't care.
別に
-You're just faking it, right? -Well, yeah, but--
単なるフリだろ フリ (菜緒)そ…そうだけど
Anyway, it's really cold. Let's go home!
んなことよりさみーから さっさと帰るぞ つご
What's with him?
(菜緒)何なの
Darn him!
もう!
We can't go in now.
ダメ今
I told you, we can't go in now!
(菜緒) ちょっ…ダメだってば こつ
-Let's go, Tetsu. -Yeah, let's.
(香織)テツ行こ ( 85 小)
That's the first time I've seen a real live kiss.
生チュー初めて見た
And right in front of us, too!
こんな人前で
Jeez! Who want's to see that?
(上原) ったく迷惑な
I guess that's normal.
まあ普通か
An elevator is pretty isolated.
エレベーターって密室だし
You see it all the time in movies.
こういう場面映画とかで よく見るもんね
But it's not like I want to kiss here too
べ…別に密室だからって 宓宏だか
just because it's isolated.
そうし1うの したいわけじゃないから
What the heck are you mumbling about?
仩原) 何をブツブツ言ってんだよ
You're supposed to be Issei's girlfriend?
(まりな) 菜緒がいっちゃんの彼女?
Yeah. And what's worse,
そう しかもいっちゃん
Issei tried to blackmail me with the money I owe for the broken dishes.
丼の弁償代の話まで 持ち出してさ のさ
But it's just while that woman's at the shop, right?
(まりな)でも店に その人がいる間だけなんでしょ
-Yeah. -What's wrong with that?
(菜緒) うん まりな)いいじゃん別に
Oh, sorry.
あっごめん
Sheesh! What a pain!
うーわうざっ!
Huh? What is it?
(菜緒)ん?何?
Just because I didn't text him for a while yesterday, he's all jealous.
昨日ちょっと 連絡しなかったぐらいで
Mitsuishi's worried about you.
みつちゃん心配なんだよ
It wasn't like a group date! We were just doing karaoke.
だって合コンつったって こつ たかがカラオケだよ?
Yeah, some guys were there, but he's getting way too possessive.
そりゃあ男の子も来るけどさ いちいち束縛しすぎ!
-I wish Uehara were more possessive. -Huh?
いいな束縛 (まりな)え? いま
That's so much more boyfriend-like.
何が彼氏って感じ
What are you talking about?
何言ってんの?
You're the one with the boyfriend that everyone wants.
誰もがうらやむ 彼氏がいるくせに
Is he really my boyfriend?
彼氏ねえ
I can't deal with you guys.
(上原)付き合いきれね
Anyway, it's really cold. Let's go home!
んなことよりさみーから さっさと帰るぞ つご
-One Miso Ramen! -OK!
(徹平)はいみそラーメン一丁! (菜緒)はーい
I'll take care of this, Nao. You get them.
よしかわ (一星)吉川ここ俺やっとくから あっちのお客さん
OK.
(菜緒)あっはーい
Here's your water.
お冷お持たせしました
I told you, I came right home after the karaoke.
(まりな) こないだはカラオケ行って すぐ帰ったって言ってんじゃん
But you still could have texted me, right?
(光石)それならそれで メールぐらいできるだろって話だよ
Jeez! Quit being so nosy!
あーもう うざいうざいうざい!
I'm not being nosy!
(光石) うざいうざい
OK, you two! Enough! This is on me.
(菜緒)はいはい... 私からのサービス
-Really? -Thanks!
(まりな)んっいいの? (光石)サンキュー
Would you two make up already?
だからいい加減 2人とも仲直りしてよ
-How is it? -Yum! Good!
ど う? (まりな) うーんおいしい な) つ
Nao, that woman's been glaring at you for a while.
それはそうと菜緒お前 さっきからずっと見られてんぞ つ
Huh?
え
Since this morning?
朝から?
Is that Issei's stalker?
まさかあの人が いっちゃんのストーカー?
Thanks! That was great!
(客)オヤジさん ごちそうさん
Yeah.
(菜緒) まあ
Oh, you're supposed to act like the girlfriend--
例の恋人のフリしてって 頼まれてるってやつ?
Shh! She'll hear you! She'll hear!
シッ!聞こえるよ 聞こえる
Dang, what a negative attitude she's got!
すげえネガティブオーラだな
Hey, Nao. Clean up the counter.
(一星)おい吉川 カウンター片付けておいてくれ
Uh... OK.
(菜緒)あっはーい
Oh! Oh!
あつあつ
How about... How about some water?
お冷…お冷いかがですか
Here's some water.
お冷どうぞ
-You're a liar. -Huh?
(ゆかり)ウソつき (菜緒)え?
You and Issei aren't a couple. That's a lie, isn't it?
やっぱり一星さんと 付き合ってるなんてウソでしょ
Oh... No...
あついや…
No, that's not...
いやそんな...
-Issei! -Yes?
BEE A (-EE) lau
Will you go on a date with me tomorrow?
明日私と デートしてくれませんか?
What?
!? え
I'm not giving up until you go on a date with me.
(ゆかり)私デートしてくれるまで 諦めませんから
What are you talking about?
何言ってんすか!
I've got a girlfriend.
俺には吉川という 彼女がいるし
Isn't that right?
なあ吉川?
Give it up. You can't fool me any more.
無駄よ 私の目はごまかせないから
We're not trying to fool you.
いや…ごまかすも何も なあ? よ
If you're going together, then why aren't you friendlier to her?
じゃあ付き合ってるのに 才合つ どうして名前で呼ばないの?
Well, uh... because we're working.
いやあの 仕事中ですから
Isn't that right, Nao?
なあ菜緒
Yeah...
(菜緒) う…うん
And you never ever touch each other.
スキンシップも全くないし
That's not true!
そんなことないよな?
You two don't give off a lovey-dovey aura at all.
そもそも 好き好きオーラがない!
Lovey-dovey aura?
好き好きオーラ?
-I love you, Nao! -Huh?
好きだ菜緒! (菜緒)え? 米
When did you two get together?
(阿部)お前らいつの間に
Nao... you and Issei are...
(阿部)吉川お前 一星さんと?
No, no, we're not, Abe!
いや…違うって あべっち!
Yes, we are!
いいや違わねえ
Issei!
一星さん!
She's got a boy--
こいつにはね 上原っていう彼
Boy, you sure want to eat curry, don't you?
カレーが食べたいって? あべっち
But this is a ramen shop.
でもここはラーメン屋だから
Here! Have some potstickers!
(光石)餃子餃子食え!
-Marina, get some soy sauce. -Here you go!
まりなまりな しようゆ (まりな) しょうゆはいよ
No, there's something fishy going on. You're hiding something.
(ゆかり)やっぱりおかしい 何か隠してるでしょ
No... No, not at all.
いやそんな…何も
At any rate, we really are a couple.
とにかく俺たちは ちゃんと付き合ってますから
Then prove it to me.
じゃあ証拠見せてよ!
Show me proof that you're lovey-dovey.
2人がラブラブな証拠 フノフノな
Proof?
しょ...証拠?
Show me all day tomorrow.
明日1日 私に見せてください
Huh? What do you mean by that?
え…どういう?
Huh? The three of you are going on a date?
(上原)ん? 3人でデート?
Uh-huh.
そう…
It just kind of ended up that the three of us would go together.
何か成り行きで
Really?
(上 )ふーん 原
Issei was at a loss for what to do.
いっちゃんすっかり参ってて
So he said if that would satisfy her, then he'd do it.
だから気が済むならって その場でオーケーしちゃつてさ
Oh, but don't worry, Uehara.
あつでも心配しないでね 上原君!
We're only doing this to convince Yukari.
これはゆかりさんを 納得させるためだから
But... if you really don't want me to go, I can tell them no.
でも上原君がイヤなら 今からでも行くの断って
Go! Go!
行け行け!
Yes!
おっしゃ!
Huh? Were you saying something?
ん?何だった?
I'm taking a bath.
お風呂入ってくる
Is he really my boyfriend?
本当に彼氏なんだよね
Wow, what a nice day!
(一星)あーいい天気だな
There's only a slight breeze. It's perfect date weather.
風は穏やかだしまさに デート日和って感じ
Don't you agree, Nao?
なあ吉川
I'm not sure I can do this.
やっぱり気が進まないな
I'm really sorry to make you do this.
(-星) 悪かったよ付き合わせて
But this will be the end of it.
でもこれで最後だから
Just play my girlfriend for today.
今日1日だけ 俺の彼女になってくれよなっ よつ
I know.
(菜緒)分かったよ
I'm here.
お待たせ
Hello.
ど...どうも
Thank you for letting me watch you today.
今日は1日 よろしくお願いします
Dang, computers are expensive.
やっぱパソコン高えなー
This is no time to be casually flipping through a magazine.
(阿部)のん気に雑誌なんか 読んでる場合じゃねーぞ上原
Cut that out, you jerk.
何だようぜえな
I came here to advise you as your close friend.
俺は親友として 忠告しにきたんだろーが!
-Since when are you my close friend? -Ouch!
誰が親友… (阿部)イッテ ツテ
Listen to me, and don't be too surprised.
いいか聞いて驚くなよ
Nao and the guy Issei she works for...
吉川な バイト先の一星さんと.
are dating!
デキてるんだ!
I'm serious! I saw them!
本当だって 俺見たんだぞ!
OK, fine. Now get out of here.
分かったから帰れよ
I've got my own work to go to.
俺これからバイトなんだけど
-Uehara! -Crap! I'm going to be late.
上原! 仩原)ヤッベ遅刻する
Jeez! You handsome guys sure don't have to worry much.
(阿部)あ~あやっぱ モテる男は余裕だよな
When Issei put his arm around Nao like that
あの吉川が一星さんに 肩抱かれてさ
it totally ticked me off, and I'm not even her boyfriend.
俺なんか彼氏でもねーのに イラッてしちゃつたよ
What should we ride first?
(一星)どうしよっかな
Probably something scary is best.
まあ最初は絶叫系かな
Right...
EJll...
Nao?
菜緒
Yeah!
そうだねいっちゃん
Oh, that looks good.
(一星)あつあれいいじゃん
Let's ride that. Come on.
あれにしようよ 行こう
I wish I could have come here with Uehara.
上原君と来たかったな
-No, not that one. -Why not?
(菜緒)やだってば (一星)何でだよ
It'll be fun.
(1星)楽しみじゃん (菜緒)やだよ!
Can you believe that the three of them are on a date together?
本当に3人で デートしちゃってるよ
But why do we have to watch them?
で何で俺たちが それをここで見てるんだ?
We're doing this for Nao's sake.
いいじゃん これは菜緒のためなんだから
How is this for Nao?
どこが菜緒のためなんだよ
I'm calling this Operation Set His Heart on Fire!
名づけて "ハートに火をつけろ大作戦"
-Oh. There they are! -I brought him.
まりな)あっ来た来た (阿部)連れてきたよ
What the heck are you guys also doing here?
ってかお前らまで 何でここにいんだよ?
We're all making sure that Nao doesn't do anything foolish.
だからみんなで吉川が 何か間違いを起こさないように
This is dumb. Don't you have anything better to do?
どんだけ暇なんだよ バカバカしい
Aah! Uehara! Have a look! Have a look!
ああ!上原君 見て見て見て
-Huh? -Look! Look! Look!
(上原)は? まりな)見て見て見て.
Hide!
隠れて!
She's supposed to be acting,
(まりな)いくら演技とはいえ あれはないよね?
I'm so worried about her.
何か心配
As her best friend, I'm concerned.
まりな親友として心配
What if things escalate between those two?
このままあの2人が エスカレートしたらどうしよう
Just let go of everything and have a great time today, OK?
(一星)今日はさ 開き直って楽しもうぜ
-I'm not sure I can. -Don't you like this kind of ride?
(菜緒)楽しめるかな (一星)絶叫系は苦手か?
Yes, I do. It's just that...
そうじゃないけど
Something is giving me a chill.
何か寒気する気がする
Oh, no. I'm scared, Uehara.
(阿部)ヤバい 上原怖いよ
Get your hands off me, jerk.
(上原)触んなうぜえな
I feel so guilty that it seems like I can hear Uehara's voice.
何か罪悪感から上原君の声 聞こえる気がするし
You got his approval, right?
あいつの許可もらったんだろ
-Yeah, but... -Uehara!
(菜緒)そうだけど (阿部)上原...
I just don't feel right about it.
(菜緒)何か気持ち上で 引っかかるっていうか
With all these couples here,
こういうカップルが多い所 来ると
it makes me think about Uehara. I wish he were here.
上原君どうしてるかなとか 上原君とデートしたい
-That was more fun than I expected. -Yeah, it was.
意外と楽しかったね (一星)そうだな
Have they always gone this fast?
こんな早かったっけ? ったつ メリ-ゴーラウンド
-Look how much it's going up and down! -It sure is.
(菜緒)見てすっごい揺れてる (一星)本当だ
Oh! Mount Fuji!
あっ富士山
Hey, look, Yukari! You can see Mount Fuji!
ねえ見てゆかりさん 富士山見えるよ!
-Fuji's totally gigantic! -It's huge!
(一星)めっちゃデカいな富士山 (菜緒)おっきい
Look! Can you see it?
ほら見える?
-It sure is pretty. -Wow!
(一星) きれいだな (菜緒)すごーい
-It's nice. -Yeah.
(一星)ねっ (菜緒)ねっ つつ ねね
Hey, this is so much fun! How come you're not riding it?
(菜緒)おーい楽しいよ 何で乗らないの?
See!
ほら
She's totally gotten into it now.
あいつ結局 ノリノリじゃねーかよ
Look, Uehara! What cool french fries!
(阿部)なあなあ上原 見て見てポテトポテト
Shut up!
うるせー!
Very nice. It seems his heart's starting to catch fire.
つんつん いい感じに火がついてきたねえ
That's kind of cruel, you know.
(光石)お前趣味悪くねーか
Who cares. I'm doing this for Nao.
(まりな)いいのいいの これも菜緒のため
You're terrible at this.
(一星)ヘタクソ
You're pretty bad too.
(菜緒)そっちだって こつ ヘタクソじゃん
Wait, Issei! Wait!
いっちゃん 待って待って…
I haven't been to an amusement park in a while. It sure is fun!
遊園地って久々に来たけど やっぱ楽しいね!
-Isn't it? -Yeah.
(一星)だろ? (菜緒) うん ろん
-Doing this is nice once in a while. -It is!
たまにはこういうのもいいよな (菜緒)ねっ
-Oh! -What?
あ (一星)何だよ
Next let's do something that you want to do, Yukari.
(菜緒)今度ゆかりさんの 好きなやつに乗ろうよ
I don't really care. Anything is fine.
別に私は何でもいい
Oh, come on. Since you're here, you may as well have fun.
そんなせっかく来たんだから てんなセつ たくさん乗ろう
Or, maybe, you've become convinced about us?
もしかして
Oh, yeah. That's right.
そうだった
I was just plain having a good time.
私ったら つにつ 普通に楽しんじゃって
Yukari,
(一星)俺ゆかりさんとは
I would hope that you could still be a regular customer
今までどおり 一番星の常連さんとして
-like you have been, and-- -I'm not convinced!
末長くお付き合いできたら… (ゆかり) まだ…
I still don't believe that you're a couple.
私まだ2人のこと 信用したわけじゃないから
Yukari--
ゆかりさん
You want me to choose the next ride, right?
次私が好きなやつで いいんだよね
Uh-huh.
うん
I've decided what I want to do.
私あれ乗りたい
Which one?
あれ?
No! No! No! No!
(菜緒)イヤイヤイヤ... !
Open the door! Come on! Open the door!
開けて! ねえねえ開け…
JIKYU GENERAL HOSPITAL
イヤイヤイヤ うわー!
Uhm, is the exit this way?
あつあの 出口ってこっちですか?
Uh, this sure must be hard work.
(阿部)あーバイトですか 大変ですね
By the way, my name is Abe Jun.
あっ僕 阿部順つていいまして
Everybody calls me Abe--
みんなからは "あべっち”って呼ばれて...
Jeez, Abe! Let's get going! Sorry about that.
(まりな)もうあべっち べつ さっさと行くよすいませんね
How can you hit on girls in a place like this?
(光石)お前よく こんなとこでナンパできるな
Jeez! That scared me!
(まりな) うお~ (光石)びっくりした
How's this job?
バイトですが?
I can't take any more of this.
(菜緒)もうダメ
I can even hear Marina's voice.
何かまりな声 聞こえてくるし
I must be hearing phantoms.
幻聴聞こえてくる
I'm so afraid, I'm losing my mind.
もう怖くて おかしくなっちゃつた
I want to go home!
あーもう帰りたいよ
-What are you doing there? -No! Leave me alone!
(上原)何してんだよ (菜緒)イヤ!イヤイヤ
Quit screaming! It's me!
(上原) うるせー! おい俺だってばおい! こつ
-Look! Look! -I'm scared.
ほらほら (菜緒) うわー!
It's me! Look!
(上原)俺だほらほら
Uehara... Why are you here?
う…上原君 何で?
I could ask you the same. Why are you alone?
仩原) お前こそ何で1人なんだよ
I so wanted to be with you.
(菜緒) 云いたかった
Let's go.
(上原)帰るぞ
Come with me.
ほら
OK.
うん
Nao!
(一星)吉川!
Huh?
え?えっ
What are all you guys doing here?
何で?何で みんなここにいるの?
Well, to tell you the truth, I happened to receive some tickets.
いやー実は たまたまチケットもらってさ
But we didn't want to interfere. Right, Mitsuishi?
でも邪魔しちゃ悪いかなーって ねえみっちゃん
Yeah. We didn't say anything, and did different stuff.
ああ黙って 別行動してたんだよ
Who's this good-looking guy?
このイケメンは?
Oh, uh... Uehara, he's...
(菜緒)あつあ 上原君はその
He's a classmate. A classmate!
(まりな)同級生です同級生!
-We're all Nao's classmates. -That's right.
みーんな菜緒の同級生 (菜緒) うん
I see.
(ゆかり)ふーん
By the way,
そういえばあれ乗った? (菜緒)え?
The Ferris wheel here has these four gondolas
ここの大観覧車 何と4台だけ
that are completely see-through.
スケルトンの ゴンドラがあるんだよ!
Wow! Cool!
(菜緒)ほほつお~
And there's this rumor
まりな)そのゴンドラに乗って
that if a couple rides in one of those and kisses at the very top,
頂上でキスしたカップルは 幸せになれるっていうね
-they'll be happy forever! -Yeah!
ジンクスあるんだよね~ (光石)ね~
Really?
(菜緒)へえ
That's so stupid. I'm going home.
アホらし 俺もう帰るわ
Come closer.
もっとこっち来いよ
Uehara.
上原君
Nao.
(上原)菜緒
I want to ride that.
乗りたいな こいな
What?
え (菜緒)あっアハハ
I really want to ride that!
私乗りたいです
Even though I said that, it's still going to be three of us.
とは言ったものの どうせ3人で乗るハメだった
I'll hold back Yukari and Issei.
私がゆかりさんといっちゃんを 引き止めるから
-Then you jump on with Uehara. -What?
その隙に上原君と乗って (菜緒)え?
I'll let you and him have the see-through one.
スケルトンのやつは 菜緒たちに譲るから
Get a kiss at the top! You can do it!
頂上で密室キス 頑張ってね!
Marina.
まりな
It'll work out. Uehara wants it too.
大丈夫 上原君もそのつもりだよ
I know you're on the same wavelength.
きっと通じ合ってる
OK.
うん
Ready? Let's do this.
いい?行くよ
Ready... Go!
rt-Do
Issei!
一星さん
Nao!
吉川
Marina.
まりな
Uehara!
上原君
-Let's get on, Issei. -You must be kidding!
(ゆかり)-星さん行きましょう (一星)マジで…
OK, Uehara and me ride together.
(阿部) じゃあ上原は俺と
Get your hands off me, you creep.
(上原︶触んな 気持ち悪いな
Ouch!
(阿部)イッテ! ツテ
Stop it! Stop it!
(菜緒)やめてやめて
Come on! You're holding up the line!
(従業員)はいはい 後がつかえてますからね
What the... Why am I all alone in here?
何で何で俺だけ もう!
Where's Nao?
(まりな)菜緒は?
Things got all messed up.
何かややこしいことに なつ なってるぞ
What the... How did it end up like that?
(まりな)何で? 何でそうなるの
Just forget about it, would you?
もうほっとけよ
How can you talk like that?
何その言い方
I mean, you don't have to go to all this trouble.
わざわざこんな 手の込んだことしなくても
Things will work out between Nao and Uehara if you leave them alone.
菜緒と上原なら ほっとけばうまくいくって
I'm not doing this... just for Nao.
別に菜緒たちだけの ためじゃないし
Huh?
ん?
We need a chance to make up too.
仲直りにも きっかけが必要だし
Mitsuishi...
みつちゃんってさ
you can see what's going on with others,
人のことは分かるけど
but you can't tell when things are wrong with yourself.
自分のことになると 全然気づかないよね
Wow! Oh my god!
(菜緒)わー!え?えっ
Marina and Mitsuishi are...
まりなとみつちゃんが
kissing in the gondola!
密室キ…
We ended up as an odd pair, didn't we?
何かおかしなペアに なっちゃつたね
Sorry.
悪かったわね
No, it's all right.
あつつつん
It's actually been a really fun day today.
なんだかんだ 今日すっごく楽しめたし
Uhm, Yukari.
ねえゆかりさん
Why do you like Issei so much?
どうしてそんなに いっちゃんのこと好きなの?
Well, I mean...
あついや…
I don't really know you,
ゆかりさんのこと よく知らないけど
but you don't look like the super aggressive type.
でもそんなに 積極的なタイプには見えないから
Because he smiled at me.
笑ってくれたから
Huh?
え?
I've never been able to smile much.
私昔から うまく笑えなくて
I was always alone, even in university.
大学でもいつも1人で
One day, I got my courage up and went to a group blind date.
ある日頑張って 合コンに行ったの
But I couldn't join the conversation.
でもやっぱり話に入れなくて
Everybody would stare at me, but act like they weren't.
みんな私のことを 見て見ぬフリして
Then on my way home...
その帰りに
Here. It's on the house.
(一星)サービスだよお客さん
Your reward for working hard today.
今日1日頑張ったご褒美
At that time
(ゆかり) あの時一星さんだけは
Issei was the only person who appreciated me for who I am.
私の存在を 認めてくれた気がした
So I began to wish that I could spend more time with him.
でこの人と少しでも 緒にいられたらって
I know it was really out of place for me to do that.
身の程知らずだって こつ 分かってるけど
No, that's not true!
そんなことない!
This is what Issei told me.
いっちゃん言ってたよ
"Yukari said good things about our ramen."
ゆかりさんが ラーメン褒めてくれたって こつ
You've encouraged Issei, Yukari.
いっちゃんもゆかりさんに 励まされたんだよ
I know that his smile was just a smile for a customer.
別に かってるし 分
-That's not true. -I'm convinced.
そんなことない… (ゆかり)もう分かってるから
I've been convinced about you two for a while.
2人のこと本当は もう認めてるから
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
I was just being spiteful.
ただちょっと 意地悪したかっただけ こかつたに
After being with you all day today, I understand now.
今日1日一緒にいて よく分かった
If you can make Issei smile like that...
あんなふうに 星さんが笑うなら
then I have to give up.
諦めるしかない
Yukari...
ゆかりさん
Sorry about
(一星)今日は悪かったな 吉川借りて
It's OK. She owes a lot to you.
あいつが いつも世話になってるから 的になっ
But I bet it ticks you off, doesn't it?
でも本当は 面白くなかっただろ
Not really.
別に
You're OK with it?
平気なのか?
Yeah, I am.
平気だけど
How can you be?
何で平気なんだよ
It's not really my place to say this,
俺が言うことじゃないけど
but when you act all cool like this,
お前があんま 余裕な顔すると
it makes her feel anxious about you.
逆にあいつが 不安がると思って
She's always smiling.
あいついつも笑ってんだよ
Huh?
(一星)ん?
She also gets angry easily,
すぐ怒るし 女又
and cries easily too.
ですぐ泣く
But she always ends up with a smile on her face.
(上原)でも最後は いつも笑ってんの
Her emotions keep her pretty busy.
忙しい奴
I think that's what's so great about her.
それがあいつの いいとこだからな
Yeah.
ああ
I'm sorry.
悪い
Maybe I didn't have to worry.
やっぱ余計なお世話だったな
It feels to me now like she and I are family.
俺何か吉川の 身内みたいな気持ちになっててさ こいな
When she first came to our shop, she was totally hopeless.
あいつうちに来た時 初めは全然ダメでさ
Every day she broke dishes and confused orders.
毎日丼割るし 剖る 注文は間違えるし
But she told me that she couldn't let her parents find out,
でも親に知らせるわけに いかないからって言って
and she worked her butt off every day.
毎日必死で頑張っててさ
You know, Nao has a kind of mysterious power.
(一星)何か不思議だよな 吉川って
I lied.
ウソ
-I lied to you. -Huh?
ウソだよ (一星)ん?
I'm not OK with this!
やっぱ俺平気じゃねーから
Jeez, dude.
(一星)何だよそれ
Oh, Marina and Mitsuishi said they're going home.
(菜緒)あつまりなとみつちゃん 先帰るって2人で
They were really lovey-dovey.
(一星)ラブラブだな フノフ こな
-Why don't we go home too? -OK.
(上原) じゃ俺らも帰るか (菜緒) うん
I'll leave you guys here.
私はここでいい
I'll say bye to you now.
ここでお別れにする
I like Evening Star ramen, but...
私一番星のラーメンは 好きだけど
I won't go there again until I can get over you, Issei.
星さんのこと忘れるまで もう店には行かないから
Yukari--
ゆかりさん
Thank you for everything today.
今日はありがとう
Thank you for all the good food you've made for me.
今までごちそうさま
Wait, Yukari!
ちょっと待って ゆかりさん!
I can't let it end like this.
やっぱダメだよこんなの
Nao.
吉川
Yukari has been very frank about how much she likes you, Issei.
ゆかりさんは いっちゃんのことが好きだって ごたつ
So you need to be frank with her too.
だからごまかしちゃ ダメなんだよ
What are you talking about?
どういうこと?
I'm very sorry, Yukari.
ゆかりさんごめんなさい
I...
私…
I'm sorry!
(一星)すいませんでした
I lied to you.
俺ウソついてました
To tell you the truth...
本当は
she's not my girlfriend at all.
こいつ俺の彼女でも 何でもないんです
I didn't want to hurt you, Yukari.
俺ゆかりさんを 傷つけるのがイヤで
So I made this all up.
ついこんなウソを
But I know that was way more cruel.
でもそのほうが ずっと失礼でしたよね
I'm terribly sorry, Yukari.
ゆかりさんごめんなさい
You see, Yukari--
あのねゆかりさん
That's enough.
もういいだろ
-Huh? -They need to settle this on their own.
(菜緒)え? (上原)あとは2人の問題だ
-But-- -This has nothing to do with us now.
でも (上原)俺たちには関係ないから
"Us"?
俺たち?
Hey! Wait!
(菜緒)えっちよっ
Sorry, Issei and Yukari!
いっちゃんゆかりさん ごめんね
Wait! Wait! Yukari!
あつあのさゆかりさん
I'm really glad I was able to talk with you.
私ゆかりさんと 話せてよかった
I mean it. Really!
本当だよ あっちょっと
I understand what you're telling me...
事情は分かったけど
but it still doesn't make sense.
何か納得できない
Everything is my fault.
全部俺が悪いんです
I forced her to do this.
俺があいつに 無理やり頼んで
That's not what I mean.
じゃなくて
Were you actually acting?
本当に演技だったんですか?
Huh?
え?
Are you sure you really have no feelings for Nao?
星さんはあの人のこと 本当に何も思ってないんですか?
Well, I mean, she's got Uehara.
だってあいつには 最初から上原がいるし
And besides, to me, she's just a co-worker.
そもそもあいつは俺にとって 仕事仲間っていうか
Let's face it, ramen is my only love.
大体俺はラーメン一筋
Or to put it another way, ramen is my girlfriend.
しいて言うなら 恋人はラーメン! ってね つ
So, you won't even acknowledge it yourself, huh?
自分のことは 見て見ぬフリが
Huh?
え?
Nothing.
何でもない
I thought you were more of a man than that, Issei.
星さんってもっと 男らしい人だと思ってた
What?
えつと
Good bye.
さよなら
Huh? Hold on!
(一星)いやちょっと…
What's that all about?
何で?
-Issei. -Huh?
一星さん (一星)あ?
-Oh, it's just you. -Did you just get dumped by your stalker?
何だお前かよ (阿部)あ もしかして
No!
(-劉ちげーよ!
Where the hell were you, anyway?
つーかお前 大体どこ行ってたんだよ!
-Let me tell you what happened to me. -Huh?
(阿部)いやー聞いてくださいよ (一星)あ?
I was just... dumped by a ghost.
俺も今 幽霊にフラれたんです
-What? -Oh, I have an idea!
(一星)は? (阿部)あつそうだ はあ
How about you and me swap sob stories?
これから一緒に 傷の舐め合いしません?
Hey! I did not just get dumped!
お前な一緒にすんじゃねーよ
-Yes you did. -Shut up, you jerk.
一緒じゃないっすか (一星) うっせーバ力 つつ
What are you grinning about. It's creeping me out.
何ニヤついてんだよ 気持ち悪いな
Well, you came and found me.
だって気づいちゃつたんだもん
Found you?
気づいた?
When I first met you,
出会った頃は上原君
I could never tell what you were thinking.
何考えてんのか よく分かんなくて
You would never pay attention to me either.
全然こっち見てくんないし
But to me at the time, that was enough.
でもそれでもいいやって 思ってて
In fact, it's like a miracle to me that we've ended up like this.
何かこうなったのも 奇跡みたいなもんだなあって こなのつ
So I've decided to enjoy myself now, no matter what happens.
だから私 今を楽しむことにしたの
You sure are on top of the world.
大げさな
Also, I was really happy today.
それにうれしかったし
About what?
何が
Because you found me in the dark at the haunted house.
お化け屋敷で暗闇の中 気づいてくれたでしょ?
It was like you could sense me, and feel my presence.
あれって私の気配とか 空気とか
That's how you found me, right?
そういうので 分かったってことでしょ?
Hey... Wait!
えっちよっ… えつ
It sure is taking long.
なかなか来ないね
Nao.
お前さ
Huh?
(菜緒)ん?
I want you to quit.
もう辞めたら?
What?
え?
Quit that job.
バイト
Why?
どうして?
You can get a job somewhere else.
いや別に 他のバイトでもいいじゃん
Like a cafe with just women.
女ばっかりのカフェとか
What's with you?
何だよ
I was...
いや…
I was just thinking how boyfriend-like that was.
何か今の 彼氏っぽいなって思って
You're goofy.
アホ
Hold the elevator!
(おばさん)ちょっと待って 乗ります!
Sorry. Let me squeeze in here.
はいごめんなさい ちょっと詰めてね
Sorry.
ごめん
Young people these days.
いいね若い子は
I'm so happy that I can hardly stand it!
(菜緒)もう本当幸せすぎ!
I never thought I'd be with you and Mitsuishi our senior year too.
まさか3年も
I'm so happy!
本当うれしいよ
I'm super happy too!
私もうれしいよ菜緒
We can complain about our boyfriends every day now.
これで毎日 彼氏のグチとか言い合えるね!
Then wouldn't it be better if I wasn't here?
じゃあ俺いないほうが よかったんじゃないの つに
Hey! I'm with you guys this year too!
(阿部)なあなあ 今年は俺も一緒だぜ
Oh, but Uehara is still in a different class.
あつでも上原君と またクラス離れちゃったね
Yeah, but I'm perfectly fine with that.
(菜緒) うーん でも全然平気
He promised to be with me at lunch and when we go home.
お昼と登下校は一緒って 約束したから 校ら
You're acting like you've got it made.
何か余裕じゃん
Did you two get closer over spring break?
春休みに絆深めちやった?
Yeah, I guess.
まあね フフッ
Is Yoshikawa Nao in here?
(女子生徒)吉川菜緒っている?
-Do you know her, Nao? -No.
(まりな)知り合い?菜緒 (菜緒) ううん
I've never seen her before, but she's a real cutie.
見ない顔だけど すつげえ美人じゃん
She sure looks pissed off though.
(光石) ってか何か すっげえ怒ってない?
Huh?
(菜緒)え?
Do you know who Yoshikawa Nao is?
吉川菜緒って知ってる?
That's her over there.
(美南)あっちだけど
What's going on?
(まりな)ちょっと..
-Oh, she's coming! -She's coming over here!
(菜緒)え...R6R6 え...米る米る まりな)来るよ
Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
(菜緒)ちよっちよつ
Are you Yoshikawa Nao?
吉川さんってあなた?
Come with me for a minute.
ちょっと顔貸してくれる?
"Come with me"?
か…顔
I'm Kitaura Nozomi.
のぞみ 私北浦希
Kitaura?
北浦さん?
I transferred in here this spring.
(希) この春から編入してきたの
Oh... you're a transfer student.
ああ転校生
No wonder I've never seen you.
どうりで見たことないと.
So, what did you want to talk to me about?
それで私に話って?
Is it true...
あなた…
that you're dating Uehara Hisashi?
ひさし 上原久志と付き合ってるって 本当?
Huh?
え?
Uh... well...
あつそれは